export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt:  "When was the IBN5100 computer first introduced?",
        optionA: "1937",
        optionB: "1975",
        optionC: "2001",
        optionD: "1984",
        answer: "B"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is CERN known for?",
        optionA: "World domination",
        optionB: "Consumer electronics",
        optionC: "Nuclear research",
        optionD: "Construction",
        answer: "C"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Who is John Titor?",
        optionA: "A time traveler",
        optionB: "A painter",
        optionC: "A musician",
        optionD: "A King",
        answer: "A"
    }
    ,
    {
        prompt: "What is Okabe's favorite drink?",
        optionA: "Coke Zero",
        optionB: "Boss Canned Coffee",
        optionC: "Mountain Dew",
        optionD: "Dr.Pepper",
        answer: "D"
    }
    ,
    {
        prompt: "When the Future Gadget Lab memebers put a bannana in the phonewave, what happened?",
        optionA:"The bannana vanished",
        optionB: "The bannana turned into a gel-nanna",
        optionC: "The bannana got burnt",
        optionD: "Nothing happned",
        answer: "B"
    }
    ,
    {
        prompt: "What was the original purpose of the phonewave?",
        optionA: "a microwave that could be controlled remotely via a phone",
        optionB: "a time machine",
        optionC: "a weapon",
        optionD: "a phone that used mircowave frequency",
        answer: "A"
    }
    ,
    {
        prompt: "What is Okabe's signature catch phrase?",
        optionA: "El Psy Kongree",
        optionB: "El Psy Kongroo",
        optionC: "So Let it Be",
        optionD: "To the Steins gate",
        answer: "B"
    }
    ,
    {
        prompt: "Where in Japan does Steins Gate take place in?",
        optionA:"Kamurocho",
        optionB:"Dotenbori",
        optionC:"Akihabara",
        optionD:"Sapporo",
        answer:"C"
    }
    ,
    {
        prompt: "What is Okabe's code name?",
        optionA:"Dr. Claw",
        optionB:"Future Solider",
        optionC:"Super Hacker",
        optionD:"Hououin Kyouma",
        answer: "D"
    }
    ,
    {
        prompt:"When does World War 3 happen?",
        optionA:"2025",
        optionB:"2015",
        optionC:"2150",
        optionD:"2011",
        answer:"B"
    }
] 